// src/data/disneyTriviaData.js
const disneyTriviaData = [
    {
      question: "What are the names of Cinderella's stepsisters?",
      answer: "Anastasia and Drizella"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Disney movie features a young boy named Mowgli who is raised by wolves?",
      answer: "The Jungle Book"
    },
    {
      question: "In 'Beauty and the Beast,' what does Belle's father invent?",
      answer: "A wood-chopping machine"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the villain in 'The Little Mermaid'?",
      answer: "Ursula"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Disney princess is known for her long, magical hair?",
      answer: "Rapunzel"
    },
    {
      question: "What kind of animal is Thumper in 'Bambi'?",
      answer: "Rabbit"
    },
    {
      question: "In 'Aladdin,' who is the Sultan's trusted advisor and the main antagonist?",
      answer: "Jafar"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of Ariel's friend who is a flounder in 'The Little Mermaid'?",
      answer: "Flounder"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Disney movie is set in ancient China and features a young woman named Mulan?",
      answer: "Mulan"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the magical land in 'The Lion King' where Simba and his friends live?",
      answer: "Pride Lands"
    }, 
    {
        question: "What is the name of Simba's father in The Lion King?",
        answer: "Mufasa"
      },
      {
        question: "Which Disney princess has a pet chameleon named Pascal?",
        answer: "Rapunzel"
      },
    
  ];
  
  export default disneyTriviaData;
  